justapinch.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Just A Pinch

Hello, hello! We have tried to make our Privacy Policy as detailed as possible so that you know exactly how your information will be used. When it comes down to it, though, our policy is a simple one: We pledge to respect your privacy as a member of this club. The recipe club is meant to be a home-away-from-home for you while you’re online and we intend to be good neighbors! 

Our legal friends aren’t fans of simplicity, though, and have asked that we “fancify” our philosophy a bit by adding in a few extra words. Please take a moment to read our handiwork below! You can also find additional information on the terms of Club membership by reviewing the Terms of Use.

Except as explicitly provided herein, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Just A Pinch Recipe Club® does not own or control, or to people that Just A Pinch Recipe Club® does not employ or manage. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. The current version of this Privacy Policy is dated May 25, 2018. 

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. You should check this Site frequently to see recent changes in this Site’s Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use. 

## 1\. What personal information is collected from me?

The types of personal information collected on these pages may include, but are not limited to, your name, email address, standard contact information including addresses and phone numbers, transactional information, and financial information such as credit card number. You also may provide additional information to us when you conduct a search on this Site, place an order for merchandise, complete a questionnaire or an entry form for sweepstakes or contests, and participate in discussions or other community features. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding, for example, your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with the services we provide and contact preferences. Wherever Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

Just A Pinch Recipe Club® may gather and collect any of the following: (1) IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer or device) to track a user’s session while the user remains anonymous, (2) computer or device and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform, (3) purchase history, (4) the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from this Site, including date and time, (5) cookie number, and (6) Web pages and/or products you viewed or searched. Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® analyzes this data for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of this Site users visit and how long they spend there. In general, we do not link your IP addresses to anything personally identifiable to you. During some visits Just A Pinch Recipe Club® may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

Just A Pinch Recipe Club® gathers and stores certain types of information whenever you use this Site or the services made available hereon (the “Services”). For example, like many Websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses this Site. Various third party companies offer utilities that are designed to allow or help you visit and use Websites anonymously; please note, however, that Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® may not be able to provide you with a personalized experience on this Site if you choose to utilize any such utilities.

## 2\. What are cookies and how are they used by Just A Pinch Recipe Club®?

Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® may place Internet cookies on your hard drive. Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are used to (a) remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service, (b) estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Website to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior, (c) track your progress and entries in promotions, sweepstakes and contests, if any, and (d) measure certain traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users’ habits are similar or different from one another. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some Web pages of this Site may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information. 

For logged-in members, performance cookies will be matched to your member account and therefore may be personally identifiable. This is required for us to provide logged-in members with all of the custom site features that come with an account, including saved settings and other account information. Without these, the site is unable to function properly for logged-in members. 

## 3\. Does Just A Pinch Recipe Club® use Web beacons, and, if so, how?

Just A Pinch Recipe Club® may employ Web beacons (also called single-pixel gifs), which are customized links or similar technologies, when sending you newsletters or promotional emails. Web beacons allow Just A Pinch Recipe Club® to (a) determine whether you have opened, or acted upon, a promotional email and which links you have clicked on in order to deliver to you more focused email communications and other information, (b) allow Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® to count the number of users who have visited certain Web pages and effectively deliver co-branded services, and (c) enable Just A Pinch Recipe Club® to compile aggregated statistics and determine the efficacy of promotions by using Web beacons from third parties, without allowing such third parties to use Web beacons on this Site to collect or access your personal information.

We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements or provide applications and services on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements or use their applications and services. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and personalized online experiences and gauge their effectiveness. 

## 4\. How is my information used?

Just A Pinch Recipe Club® will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. In general, the information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with Just A Pinch Recipe Club®. 

Members acknowledge consent to publish their user-submitted recipes and related content – including name and image - on the Just A Pinch Recipe Club® website as well as for all other purposes which may include, but are not limited to, press releases, newspaper articles, and advertising materials. 

We want to help you quickly find information regarding the Services on this Site and alert you to specific offers, updated information, and other new products and Services that are available. Accordingly, we may send you direct mailings about our various products and Services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply “opt-out” by the means provided for (if any) in the mailings or by contacting help@justapinch.com. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Just A Pinch Recipe Club® does research on our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of this Site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. Just A Pinch Recipe Club® may share this aggregated data with others. Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® also may combine your information with information we collect or receive from other companies and sources (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services.

## 5\. What does “opt-out” mean?

To “opt-out” means that you have notified Just A Pinch Recipe Club® that we no longer have permission to use your information for a particular purpose. For example, when we send you information on a new product, you will be given the opportunity to “opt-out” of receiving such information in the future.

## 6\. Who is collecting my information?

Information is collected on the Site by or on behalf of Just A Pinch Recipe Club®. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Just A Pinch Recipe Club® or an agent for Just A Pinch Recipe Club®, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular Service or purchasing those particular goods.

Please be aware that advertisers that may have links on this Site may collect personal information about you through the use of cookies, JavaScript, Web beacons, and other technologies. Just A Pinch Recipe Club® does not have any control over or access to such technologies that may be used by these advertisers, and the information practices of those Websites linked to this Site either through advertisements or other hyperlinks are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® does not, however, provide any personally identifiable information about you to these advertisers. 

For visitors generating from the EU and EEA, advertising cookies are automatically not used for personalization and all advertising on the site will be generic and non-targeted. 

For more information on cookies, please visit our Cookie Policy.

## 7\. With whom does Just A Pinch Recipe Club® share my information?

Just A Pinch Recipe Club® may share the personal data you provide or the information gathered by Just A Pinch Recipe Club® to any party with your consent or, in any event, to Just A Pinch Recipe Club® subsidiaries, agents, contractors and our business partners. Just A Pinch Recipe Club® also may share information with the following groups: (a) affiliated business which Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® does not control but with which it engages in joint and co-branded offerings, (b) third party service providers in order to facilitate the performance of only those functions which are assigned to them, such as website operation and maintenance, order fulfillment, data analysis, marketing assistance, provision of search results and links, credit card payment processing, and customer service, and (c) entities with which Just A Pinch Recipe Club® may merge or which may acquire all or substantially all of Just A Pinch Recipe Club ®’s assets, as customer information likely will be one of the transferred assets. 

Third party vendors, including Google, show Just A Pinch Recipe Club® ads on sites on the internet and utilize cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Just A Pinch Recipe Club®. To opt out of third party vendors' use of cookies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page. <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

In addition, Just A Pinch Recipe Club® believes it is necessary to share information in order to (x) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, and violations of the Terms of Use, (y) respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, and (z) establish or exercise our legal rights, or defend against legal claims, and as otherwise required by law. Except as provided above or in the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale of all or substantially all of Just A Pinch Recipe Club®’s assets, we will not share any of your information with any third party without your permission.

## 8\. How do I access, update or delete my information?

You can request the individual information that Just A Pinch Recipe Club® has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your information, remove personal information from Just A Pinch Recipe Clubs databases and/or update your personal information here on the Website or by contacting help@justapinch.com.

## 9\. What else should I know about my privacy?

Third party Internet Websites and services accessible through this Site have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Just A Pinch Recipe Club® has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process, and any transmission by you of information is done at your own risk.

## 10\. Children.

The Site is not intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any personal information submitted by visitors to the Site who are under the age of 13.

## 11\. Security.

Just A Pinch Recipe Club® uses its best efforts to protect your personal information and, to that end, uses tools such as encryption, passwords, and physical security to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no website can be absolutely secure, and third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from this Site. Therefore, although Just A Pinch Recipe Club ® works very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain absolutely private.

## 12\. Other legal notices.

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Tennessee.

## 13\. Contact us

If you have any concern about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send a thorough description to help@justapinch.com, and we will try to resolve it.

Just A Pinch Recipe Club, LLC   
782 Melrose Ave  
Nashville, TN 37211  
p. 615-599-8751  
f. 615-599-8752
